draytek.com 2017-06-22

# Home - DrayTek Corp.

You are welcome to visit DrayTek website (hereinafter referred to as "Site"). In order to make you feel comfortable using the services and information of this website, we would like to inform you of our privacy policy to protect you. Please read the following:

**The scope of application of privacy protection policy**

The content of the Privacy Policy, including how the Site handles personally identifiable information collected when you use the Site Services. The Privacy Policy does not apply to linked sites outside of the Site or to persons who are not authorized to participate or participate in the administration of this Site.

**Personal data collection, processing and use**

When you visit this website or use the functional services provided on this website, we will ask your necessary personal information and use it within that specific purpose; without your agreement in writing this website will not use your personal data for any other purpose.

When you use interactive features such as mailboxes and surveys, this site will retain your name, e-mail address, contact information and usage time. In normal browsing, the server will record the relevant actions, including the IP address of the device you are using, the time of use, the browser you are using, the browsing and data logging, etc., as a reference for our website services. This record for internal applications will not be announced.

Statistics and analysis of collected questionnaires, statistics or descriptive text of the results will be provided for accurate service. In addition to internal research, statistical data and descriptive text will be published if it is necessary. The information published excludes information on specific individuals.

**The protection of information**

The website hosts are equipped with firewall, anti-virus system and other related information security equipment and the necessary security measures to protect the site and your personal information with strict protection measures. Only authorized personnel can access your Personal data. The relevant processing personnel are signed confidentiality contract, if there is breach of confidentiality obligations, will be subject to the relevant legal punishment.

In the event that it is necessary to entrust other units to provide services for business purposes, the Site will strictly require compliance with the confidentiality obligations and take the necessary inspection procedures to ensure that it will comply.

**External links to the site**

The web pages of this website provide links to other websites. You may also click through the links provided on this website to access other websites. But the linked site does not apply to this site's privacy policy. You must refer to the privacy policy of the linked site. 

**The policy of sharing personal information with the third party**

This website will not provide, exchange, rent or sell any of your personal information to other individuals, groups, private enterprises or public agencies. However the legal basis or contractual obligations are excluded. 

The foregoing proviso includes, but not limited to:

  * You agree in writing.
  * The law states.
  * To save your life, body, liberty or property from danger.
  * In cooperation with an official or academic institution, the public interest is necessary for statistical or scholarly research, and the information is processed by the provider or collected in such a way that it does not identify a particular party.
  * Disclosure of your personal data by the Site management unit for the purpose of identifying, contacting or taking legal action as a result of your site's conduct, breach of the Terms of Service or any damage or disruption to the Site or other user interests or damage to any person .
  * Benefit your interests.
  * When commissioned by the Company to assist in the collection, processing or use of your personal data, the Site will do its best to supervise the management of the subcontractor or individual.

**The use of Cookie**

In order to provide you with the best possible service, we use cookies to improve the services of our website. The cookie is a file that contains a small amount of information stored on your computer or browsing devices. It collects relevant records such as browsing behavior and information, but does not contain Identification of your personal data, records. This site uses only the necessary cookies to measure and provide you with better service. If you do not want to accept the cookie, you can set the privacy level to High in the browser function you use to reject cookies. However it may lead to certain features of the site not working properly. 

**Amendment to the Privacy Policy**

The privacy policy of this site will be amended at any time in accordance with the needs. The revised terms will be published on the website.
